<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name='about'>About</string>
  <string name='about_text'>
    Password Safe is a password database utility. Users can keep their passwords securely encrypted on their computers. A single Safe Combination unlocks them all.\n\nPassword Safe protects passwords with the Twofish encryption algorithm, a fast, free alternative to DES. The program\'s security has been thoroughly verified by Counterpane Labs under the supervision of Bruce Schneier, author of Applied Cryptography and creator of the Twofish algorithm.\n
  </string>
  <string name='add_record'>Add Record</string>
  <string name='app_name'>Password Safe</string>
  <string name='confirm'>Confirm</string>
  <string name='create_database'>Create Database</string>
  <string name='database_name'>Database Name</string>
  <string name='delete_record'>Delete Record</string>
  <string name='destroy_database'>Destroy Database</string>
  <string name='help'>Help</string>
  <string name='help_text'>
    What is a database?\nA database is a place to group and store records.\n\nHow do I create a database?\nClick on the 'Create Database' button.\n\nHow do I open a database?\nClick on the database to be opened.\n\nHow do I change a database's name and/or password?\nThis feature is in the works.\n\nHow do I destroy a database?\nLong click the database to be destroyed then click 'Destroy Database'.\n\nWhat is a record?\nA record holds the information associated with an account.  It includes the URL for the site, the username, password, etc.\n\nHow do I add a record?\nClick on the 'Add Record' button.\n\nHow do I view or modify a record?\nClick on the record to be viewed or modified.\n\nHow do delete a record?\nLong click on the record to be deleted then click 'Delete Record'.  Alternatively, view the record, then press 'MENU', then click the 'Delete Record' menu option.\n\nHow do I use a database created by another Password Safe client?\nThis feature is in the works.\n\nHow do I use a database created by this app in another Password Safe client?\nThis feature is in the works.\n
  </string>
  <string name='passphrase'>Passphrase</string>
  <string name='save'>Save</string>
  <string name='url'>URL</string>
  <string name='username'>Username</string>
</resources>
